wants to hit the cocu that wants to hit you that
quiere pegar el cocu que te quiere pegar
he says that yes he thinks that if he is
que él dice que sí se piensa que si se
going to take it off the rapist two two
lo va a quitar los violador dos dos
things two
cosas dos
[Music]
[Música]
things pay attention to what I'm going to say eh pay
cosas atentos a lo que voy a decir eh
attention To what I'm going to say eh that
atentos A lo que voy a decir eh que
between Dallas don't [ __ ] with me Eh don't [ __ ] with me
entre Dallas no me jodas Eh no me jodas
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
what what the
qué qué
[ __ ] what's he doing what's going on churra
[__] qué hace qué pasa churra pelea de
YouTube fight What's up What's up you
youb Qué tal Qué
've entered a key moment in which
tal has entrado en un momento clave en
these people were going to pull their
el que esta gente se iban a tirar de los
hair out but in the end
pelos pero al final jugó
cageta played between cco and rups nobody wants to
cageta entre cco y rups nadie quiere
talk man everyone plays cogona today Things are
hablar tío todos juegan cagona hoy Qué
bad I'm interviewing Windy that I
mal está el patio yo entrevisto a windy
know that you for example Javi No you
que yo sé que tú por ejemplo Javi No no
're not a big fan of Windy it's clear
eres muy fanático de windy está claro
that Windy has done bad things in the
que windy ha hecho cosas mal en el
past that's the first thing I tell him let's
pasado es lo primero que le digo yo a
see I'll tell you one thing but we'll
ver yo te digo una cosa pero estaremos
agree we'll agree that
de acuerdo estaremos de acuerdo que
even if he has done bad things they have also
aunque haya hecho cosas mal también le
done things to him that perhaps the magnitude
han hecho cosas que quizá la magnitud
with which the peso has fallen is undue it
con la que ha caído el peso es indebido
's crazy just like what has happened F
es una locura igual que lo que ha pas F
of the few channels of  salseo that
de los pocos canales de salseo que la
supported her and that she was against the Bull
apoyaba y que estaba en contra del Bull
whatever And such But I don't
que sea Y tal Pero no estoy tampoco de
agree either that now because Ari and Juan have
acuerdo en que ahora porque Ari y Juan
already messed up they have shown their faces about
ya la han liado han mostr la cara lo de
ccu about Auro about villin about River
ccu lo de Auro lo de villin lo de River
and all that stuff now windy here
y todo el rollo ahora windy se aquí
admirable he was right in everything poor
admirable tenía la razón en todo pobre
me neither and I think that in the podcast believe
yo tampoco y creo que en el podcast cre
in the podcast it is not understood no
en el podcast tampoco se da entender no
no in the podcast no but the reaction of
no en el podcast no pero la reacción de
the people in the networks has been like but they
la gente en en redes ha sido como pero
are extremists they are everything all or
son extremistas son de todo de todo o
nothing that is the problem of the networks that is the
nada es el problema de las redes ese es
problem I mean in the end I think that
el problema o sea al final Yo creo que
people when I do them for example
la gente cuando les hago yo por ejemplo
an interview The objective is that they are
una entrevista El objetivo es que sean
honest I The only condition that I
honestos yo La Única condición que les
ask of them is can you tell your story
pido es podéis contar vuestra historia
where are you going I'm going to wake up aas that
dónde vas el voy a despertar aas que
is and I was going to talk i am going to talk since
es y iba a habar i a hablar ya que
we have aas let's go let's ask about the
tenemos aas vamos vamos a preguntar por
guy who has come Here we go I
tío que ha venido Aquí
came here to talk about my book
vamos he venido aquí hablar de mi libro
when he goes to the r it is that
cuando se vaya al r es que nos va a
the r is going to interrupt us but what do you think of
interrumpir el r pero qué opinas de
Well but let's go to the
Bueno pero vamos a que el tiempo de
Dallas time is quoted there is that  take advantage of it let's take
Dallas cotiza hay que aprovecharlo vamos
advantage of the fact that Dallas has come
a aprovechar que ha venido Dallas
ask him go on Javi you have the [ __ ]
pregúntale va Javi que tienes la [__]
exclusive damn about Windy what do you think
exclusiva [__] de lo de windy có qué te
the podcast the interview
aparece a ti la el podcast la entrevista
the reaction and such what we're
la reacción y tal lo que estamos
talking about basic Well I think I would repeat
hablando básic Bueno creo que repetiría
basically the same thing I said in my
básicamente lo mismo que dije en mi
video that I made a mini
vídeo que hice yo un mini vídeo
documentary video at the time on the subject
documental en su momento sobre el tema
of Windy I would repeat exactly the same thing
de windy repetiría Exactamente lo mismo
or rather in fact Eh I also mentioned this
o sea de hecho Eh Esto se lo comenté
to them when we met eh that I
también a ellos cuando quedamos eh que
really feel that the beginning of the
realmente siento que el inicio de la ola
new wave of eh Not seeing Windy as the worst
nueva de eh No ver a windy como la peor
person in the world and Ari as the best
persona del mundo y a Ari como la mejor
person in the world begins to emerge as a result of
persona del mundo empieza a salir a raíz
the documentary video that I made at the
del vídeo documental que hago yo en su
time and from there a lot
momento y de ahí empiezan un montón de
more people start to subscribe to that same
más personas a suscribirse a esa misma
opinion that I say in the first place
opinión que digo yo en un primer lugar
that at that time everyone was
que en ese momento todo el mundo estaba
against Windy because the
en contra de windy porque justo acaba de
strike that he put on Juan had just happened
ocurrir lo del strike que le puso a Juan
and in and and right after it was the
y en y y justo después fue lo del
Archangel Gabriel thing that between Archangel
Arcángel Gabriel que entre el Arcángel
Gabriel that happened but from the est ju thing
Gabriel eso pas pero de de lo del est ju
to the Archangel thing a couple of years passed
a lo del Arcángel pasaron un par de años
no  no no it didn't happen that long eh it took a couple
no no no pasó tanto eh que pasó un par
of years because I knew Juan and Ari
de años porque yo conocía a Juan y Ari
when the strike thing that was s that
Cuando lo cuando lo del strike que fue s
was in 2020 a couple of years of
eso fue en 2020 un par de años de
relationship with them or a year or two or a year and a
relación con ellos o un año o dos o año
half and what happened, maybe I
y medio y y pasó lo de la puede que
have the dates a little wrong but the
tenga las fechas un poco mal pero la
point is that I subscribe to the same thing
cuestión es que me suscribo a lo mismo
that I said in my video basically and she
que dije en mi vídeo básicamente y os
gave you a good impression when I met her 100%
dio buena impresión cuando la conocí 100
person is she good people or what Yes to me she
persona es buena gente o qué Sí a mí me
seems like a totally different girl than the one
parece una tía totalmente distinta a la
in the videos I mean in fact I'm not going to
de los vídeos o sea de hecho no te voy a
lie to you in my head it was going to be a
mentir en mi cabeza iba a ser un podcast
Flow podcast when Dallas came you know like
Flow cuando vino Dallas sabes en plan
pum pum pum and then I saw her zen mode super
pum pum pum y luego la vi modo zen super
spiritual super taking care of the line super
espiritual super cuidando la línea super
chill I mean it's a facet that I said look you
chill o sea es una faceta que dije mira
know what seeing as that you go with that
sabes qué en vista de que vas de ese
plan let's show that side of you
plan vamos a mostrar esa faceta tuya
because I don't want to condition it to let's
porque tampoco quiero yo condicionar a
put [ __ ] because it's not the
vamos a meter [__] porque no es el
Flow that she leads so that's why the
Flow que ella lleva entonces por eso el
podcast was chill there was no taser there was
podcast fue chill no hubo taser no hubo
nothing but because it is like that then
nada pero porque es que es así luego
Twitter has done crazy Twitter things
Twitter ha hecho cosas de Twitter una
the last time  you do taser
locura la última vez que no haces taser
eh I'll find you an editor the truth is I would
eh te busco yo un editor yo la verdad me
like to stay longer but I'm not going to
gustaría quedarme más pero no me voy a
stay much longer mainly because
quedar mucho rato más que nada porque
I'm very sleepy and I've been driving for many
tengo mucho sueño y he conducido muchas
hours So yes yes yes
horas Entonces
yes I'm
sies sí sí sí estoy
overcome ua ask one question no
superado úa pregunta una pregunta no
three or four listen to me the cocu wants to hit you he
tres o cuatro escúchame te quiere pegar
wants to hit you he says
el cocu que te quiere pegar que él dice
yes he thinks that if he's going to take it
que sí se piensa que si se lo va a
away the rapist two two things two
quitar lo violador dos dos cosas dos
things he wants you he wants to hit you because that's
cosas te quiere te quiere pegar porque
the way he has of proving
es la manera que él tiene de demostrar
his right or not No I mean here if they hit more
su razón o no No o sea aquí si pegan más
or less then you're right or you're telling the truth
o menos pues tienes la razón o dices la
And now you report him You yes
verdad Y que ahora lo denuncies Tú sí
like But if he reported you
que como Pero si te denunció el año
last year at least 25 times
pasado 25 veces por lo
yes totally totally makes no
menos sí totalmente totalmente no tiene
sense at all Well it's that you've
ningún tipo de sentido Bueno ya es que
already said it you published several
ya lo has dicho tú publicaste varias
things that I said is that exactly what you
cosas que dije es que tal cuál lo que
have said makes no
has dicho tú no tiene ningún tipo de
sense besides that any person with
sentido además que cualquier persona que
two fingers of brain thinks
tenga un dos deditos de frente piensa
how am I going to report him it doesn't make
cómo le voy a denunciar yo a él no tiene
any sense at all it's that you report him
ningún sentido es que que le denuncies
that you take him to trial for something
que tú lo lleves a juicio por una cosa
that he  has done to another person of course it
que él le ha hecho a otra persona claro
doesn't make any sense of course it can't
no tiene ningún sentido claro no se
be yes I
puede sí yo la verdad es que
honestly don't I don't I don't I mean yes
honestamente no no termino de O sea sí
yes I understand that I get angry and all
sí entiendo de que yo le de rabia y todo
that because I'm the only one who talked about
eso porque soy el único que habló sobre
him and who exposed him and all that but I
él y que le expuso y todo el rollo pero
don't understand I mean I don't understand what's
no entiendo la O sea no entiendo que es
going through his head to
lo que se le pasa por la cabeza para
think that by challenging me to hit me or something like that he's
pensar que por retarme a pegarme o algo
going to be more or less
del estilo va a tener más razón o menos
right or whatever I mean I mean
razón o lo que sea quiero decir o sea
besides that the idiot doesn't
además de de eso es que el tonto no
have the slightest idea what he's
tiene ni la más remoti de donde se está
getting into the guy is absolutely
metiendo el tío es absolutamente
pathetic
patético a la hora de pelear se entrenó
when it comes to fighting he trained for a few months in boxing it's like you're telling me it's a joke he doesn't have the slightest idea but it's that it doesn't matter I could even lose which would never happen in my life but I could lose and that would
en la vida pero podría yo perder y eso
n't prove him right either logical
no le daría la razón a él tampoco lógico
but of course I mean it's that it's
pero claro o sea es que es que es
absurd of course it's something that would never
absurdo claro entee es algo que jamás
happen he could hit you more because he's
sucedería te puede pegar más porque sea
stronger because he's more used to it to the
más fuerte porque esté más acostumbrado
streets or whatever but  that doesn't
a a al callejeo o lo que sea pero eso no
take away or give you the truth, I mean it
te quita ni te da la verdad o sea es que
's completely
es completamente
literal. Now with this last one, well, I said,
deut literal Ya esta última pues dije
look, you know what, if you're so
mira sabes qué que si tienes tantas
keen on doing it, we'll do it because in the
ganas de hacerlo lo hacemos porque al
end I think that's going to be the only
final creo que esa va a ser la única
justice that he's going to be able to get
justicia que va va a poder obtener por
somewhere, you know, I left him
alguna para algún lado sabes que le deje
crippled for the rest of his life, I think it
cojo para el resto de su vida creo que
's secular to get, listen. Who, why did
es laica obtener escucha A quién a que
I change the microphone? I was going to tell you, the
me cambiado el micro te iba a decir yo
only thing I want to clarify, I swear I'm
lo único que quiero matizar te lo juro
still laughing my ass off to this day at the
me sigo descojonando a día de hoy la
phrase "don't cry when
frase de luego no llores cuando te salte
a leg jumps off your leg," a leg jumps out of
una pierna te salte una pierna de su
place. But I've left it, I've
sitio Pero yo lo he dejado yo lo he
left it, eh. Because I already went to teles,
dejado eh Porque ya me fui a teles
salsea, live, in which Dallas told him,
salsea directo en el que Dallas le decía
you know what, we're going to do it. But let him know
sabes qué vamos a hacerlo Pero que sepa
that if I leave you crippled, you're screwed. He said
que si te dejo cojo te jodes ha dicho
something else afterwards, no, no, what he
algo más el después no no lo que ha
did was like a tweet that was
hecho ha sido darle like a un tweet que
supporting him, which was a screenshot
le estaba apoyando que era una captura
where his tweet and mine appeared and it said
donde salía su tweet y el mío y ponía
support for ccu 100% and he liked it and
apoyo a ccu 100% y él le dio like y
when he realized it, I think that's what he
cuando se dio cuenta yo creo que de que
liked  out of time he took away the
le dio like fuera de tiempo le quitó el
like Ah very well Ah And also there was
like Ah muy bien Ah Y también hubo otra
something else that he started saying I don't know if it's
cosa que se puso a decir No sé si es
recent from the Stream that he was doing I
reciente del Stream que estaba haciendo
don't have the slightest idea eh I
no tengo ni la más remota idea eh se lo
sent it to a del before who started saying I do
mandé a a del antes que se puso a decir
n't know if you have commented here that he
No sé si lo habéis comentado aquí que se
started saying that nimu e only
puso a decir que nimu e únicamente le
condemned her because she was trying to
condenó porque ella estaba intentando
get out of the funa I have it here I have it
salir de la funa lo tengo aquí lo tengo
here to watch it with her now when
aquí para verlo con ella ahora cuando
this let me put a clip for you man I
esto déjame que te ponga un clip tío les
thank you both from the bottom of my heart for turning a
agradezco de corazón a los dos por hacer
deaf ear to crows who talk talk and
oído sordo a cuervos que hablan hablan y
talk and then they are going to have to
hablan y que después van a tener que
take responsibility for what they said later they are going to have to
hacerse cargo de lo que dijeron después
take [ __ ] responsibility for what they
van a tener que hacerse [__] cargo de lo
[ __ ] said and when they have to
que [__] dijeron y cuando se tengan que
take responsibility Ah ah Oh it's not a joke it's not a
hacer cargo Ah ah Ay no es joda no es
joke it's not they think it's a joke they
joda no lo es piensan que es un chiste
think they are YouTube views
piensan que son visitas de YouTube
enjoy the YouTube views Because
disfrutar las visitas de YouTube Porque
then comes the reality the reality is
después viene la realidad la realidad es
that he wants to
que te quiere
hit you but the lawsuit hasn't arrived of
pegar pero la demanda no ha llegado
course let's see it's a little Well there are
claro a ver es que un poco Bueno hay
some cases where it is I mean let's see you
algunos casos donde es O sea a ver tú
when even if you know a lot about
cuando aunque sepas mucho de artes
martial arts whatever when  there is a
marciales la que sea cuando hay una
huge difference in weight and height it
diferencia muy grande de peso y altura
is absurd it is a circus
es absurdo eso es un es un circo
trying to organize a coherent fight
intentar organizar un combate coherente
in this regard because in the end there is
al respecto de eso porque al final
always someone who weighs much more than
siempre alguien que pesa mucho más que
you or is much taller than you unless it
tú o mide mucho más que tú a menos que
is a complete ignorant imbecile who
sea un completo ignorante imbécil que no
has no more remote as he
tenga más remot como
is not capable of it you cannot make a
no es capaz de no se puede hacer un
coherent fight however this guy
combate coherente sin embargo este tipo
Yes because I think he is only a
Sí porque creo que mide apenas unos un
couple of centimeters taller than me and
par de centímetros más que yo nada más
with that it could be organized
con lo cual se podría organizar
perfectly I mean it is something 100% viable
perfectamente o sea es algo 100% viable
I think that he is not seeing you
Yo creo que que él no te está a ver él
what he is trying to tell you with this is that he
lo que te está queriendo decir con esto
wants to beat you up but he
es que te quiere partir la cara pero no
is not talking to you about organizing a fight
te está hablando de organizar un combate
so that you go to the well I talk about
para que tú vayas a la bueno hablo de
boxing I talk about boxing but to me the truth is
boxeo hablo de boxeo pero a mí la verdad
boxing seems too too much it
el boxeo me parece demasiado demasi es
seems to me that they do nothing
que me parece que no se hacen nada
sincerely I mean they do
sinceramente O sea no se hacen
absolutely nothing and it seems to me like a total
absolutamente nada y me parece una total
joke sincerely With all due
payasada sinceramente Con todo el
respect to the people who love
respeto para la gente que le encante el
boxing and all that But I don't
boxeo y todo eso Pero a mí no no me
like boxing at all because it seems very
gusta nada el boxeo porque me parece muy
light too light so if I am going to
light demasiado leve entonces si yo voy
accept something like that for a clown  a
a aceptar algo así para un payaso un
circus bumpkin who is dedicated to saying
garrulo de circo que se dedica a decir
these things that this is the second time he does it
estas que es la segunda vez que lo hace
because we are doing something right and you
pues al mos hacemos algo bien y te
remember me for the rest of your life no
acuerdas de mí el resto de tu vida no
but he told you like this because he is
pero él te lo ha dicho así porque está
on social media but what he wants to tell you
en redes pero é lo que te quiere decir
is like the typical chai of plazol he says
es como el típico cani de plazol dice
says rups that he is in the waiting room I have
dice rups que está en la sala de espera
already written to him I told him to
ya ya le he escrito le he dicho que se
wait a second that he wants to go to
espere un segundo que se quiere ir a
sleep Now that he finishes telling us
dormir Ahora que nos termine de contarlo
about coscu and the entrance But well, make
de coscu y la entra Pero bueno que se
sure that the microphone works, go
asegure de que funcione el micro vay a
face what m does not work that well,
se cara lo m no funcione que pues nada
man I mean basically it seems to me Well,
tío O sea que básicamente me parece Pues
that kani is the typical chai who is
eso de kani el típico cani que te está
telling you I have no arguments against you I
diciendo no tengo argumentos contra ti
hit you it's like the [ __ ] accept something
te pego es como [__] acepta algo
intelligent a debate what do you have there
inteligente un debate tú qué tienes ahí
about the chic because of course me in front of that
de la chic porque claro yo ante esa
photograph I am very curious to
fotografía Tengo mucha curiosidad por
know his version his argument Hey, maybe
saber su versión su argumento Oye que a
the kid has a version to
a lo mejor el chaval tiene una versión
tell us Hey, go up to a debate
que contarnos Oye pues sube a un debate
with the person who has the most diffusion of the one
con la persona que más difusión tiene de
that is good I think
la que está bueno Yo creo que
mainly the I don't think so Javi but it's
principalmente la No creo no Javi pero
impossible  that he has a version
es imposible que tenga una versión
because I have invited him eight times to the
porque yo lo he invitado ocho veces al
podcast I have denied the 8 so being
podcast he denegado las 8 entonces
able to go to a place where I was
pudiendo haber ido a un lugar donde yo
going to give him good treatment Honestly I was
lo iba dar un buen trato Honestamente le
going to treat him with respect eh No he hasn't
iba a tratar con respeto eh No no ha
come So if he hasn't come to a
venido Entonces si no ha venido a un
place where they are going to treat him well and I
lugar donde lo van a tratar bien y le
am going to let him tell his story
voy a dejar contar su historia
calmly not like Dallas who surely
tranquilamente no como Dallas que seguro
the slightest thing he says something will cut him off
que la mínima que le diga algo le corta
and give him an argument and a
y le mete un argumento y un
counterargument but there he had an
contraargumento sino que ahí tenía modo
easy way him against nobody Even so he has not
fácil él contra nadie Aún así no ha
accepted how is he going to accept a debate with
aceptado cómo va a aceptar un debate con
Dallas who has proposed a fight
Dallas que le ha propuesto un combate
because he thought that Dallas was not going to accept
porque pensaba que no iba a aceptar
but Dallas has accepted this is
Dallas pero Dallas ha aceptado esto es
a person that this this that what he has
una persona que esto esto que lo que ha
done today on Twitter the explosion is
hecho hoy en Twitter la explosión esta
also writing in capital letters and this
además escribiendo en mayúscula y esta
theory is his condition it is his way of
teoría es su condición es su manera de
being that he has had all his life just like what
ser que ha tenido toda la vida igual que
this with this girl then the
lo de esto con esta chica luego salió lo
caprim min came out I mean it is something that is his
de caprim min o sea es algo que es su
way of being it is his person no this is not
forma de ser es su persona no esta no es
a person that you could do for
una persona que tú pudieras hacer por
example the debate that you did with Dallas
ejemplo el debate que hiciste con Dallas
and with they come to blows it is a person
y con llegan a las manos es una persona
that you could not do to debate and
que no podrías hacer de debatir y de
argue and such there is no time to say
argumentar y tal no hay un momento
because he is not a person who is prepared
suelta un porque no es una person parada
to argue, to argue, to
para argumentar para discutir para
apologize exactly because it is what
disculparse mismamente porque es lo que
I have said many times let's see you have
yo he dicho muchas veces vamos a ver tú
grown up in an environment where
te has criado en un ambiente en el que
this was normal or you did not see it as serious
esto era normal o no lo veías tan grave
or whatever same apologize that there is an
o lo que sea mismo discúlpate que hay un
audio recorded of you saying that the girl
audio tuyo grabado diciendo que la chica
who entered your brother I do not know what fault
que en tu hermano entró no sé qué culpa
now people can say anything else No
ya la gente puede decir más nada No
because of course not even that is a lie
porque claro es que ni eso es mentira
because I am going to hit you yes literally it is It is that it
porque te voy a pegar sí literalmente es
is extremely pathetic
Es que es que es extremadamente patético
really anything whatever however you
de verdad cualquier cualquier cosa por
take it is that it is literally it is
donde lo tomes es que es literalmente es
or what you have said a neighborhood thug
o lo que has dicho tú un cani de barrio
who does not even know what he is saying
que no sabe ni lo que está diciendo
So since he has no arguments to
Entonces como no tiene argumentos para
respond, what he does is [ __ ] and
responder pues lo que hace es [__] y
threaten what happens is that I think the
amenazar lo que pasa es que creo que el
guy I don't even know why the first time I
tío ni siquiera se porque la primera vez
passed by I completely ignored him, it did not
pasé le ignoré por completo no me
seem even coherent to
pareció ni siquiera coherente
answer him But this second time he
responderle Pero esta segunda me ha
caught me with friends And what do I know It was
pillado con colegas Y qué sé yo Ha sido
like you are going to do me what do I
como que me vas a hacer tú qué te
burst you clown and that's it and I was
reviento payaso y ya está y me estaba
laughing for a while I did not expect your
riendo un rato no me esperaba tu
answer I believed myself  that you were going to happen and no no
respuesta yo me creía que ibas a pasar y
no I'm not serious I mean it's
no no no te lo digo en serio o sea es
something that he doesn't have he doesn't
algo que ya es que no tiene es que no
have a [ __ ] clue if the guy really
tiene ni [__] idea si realmente el tío
agreed to do that I'm telling you he comes out lame
aceptara hacer eso te lo digo sale cojo
from there hey about for the rest of his
de ahí oye lo de para el resto de su
[ __ ] life and the deprimen that has been left
[__] vida y lo de primen que ha quedado
neither the what
tampoco el qué
debate challenged her to debate Ah no no no
debate la retado a debatir Ah no no no
well eh You already saw what happened
bueno eh Ya lo viste lo que lo que pasó
on Twitter the guy basically when I
en Twitter el tipo básicamente cuando le
told him to do a face to face
dije de que hiciera un cara a cara pues
the idiot responded you're forcing the
el tonto respondió estás forzando la
interaction that was when I
interacción entonces fue cuando yo le
told him I said Well and he
dije le dije Bueno y te ha puesto
also told you [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] ass no
también [__] [__] [__] [__] culo no
or something like that he told you exactly
o algo así te ha puesto exactamente
exactly I said something to that like
exactamente le dije algo a eso de que
yes don't respond And then then
que sí que no responda Y entonces luego
the guy I don't know if you saw that he responded
el tipo No sé si viste que respondió
saying Ah coscu he already said that what he
diciendo Ah coscu ya ha dicho que lo que
did was wrong and I have also said it I do
hizo estaba mal y yo también lo he dicho
n't know what And it is how it is like
no sé qué Y es como es o sea
literally either you're lying because you know you're lying
literalmente o mientes porque sabes que
Then you're evil or
estás mintiendo Entonces eres malvado o
you're lying without having a [ __ ] clue Then
mientes sin tener ni [__] idea Entonces
you're stupid there is no other option or you
eres tonto no hay no hay otra opción o
're very stupid or you're very evil and that's it he did
eres muy estúpido o eres muy malvado y
n't say it yeah  make two
ya está no lo ha dicho si hag dos
options and I would be embarrassed it would be
opciones y a mí me daría vergüenza sería
this type I'm really telling you I've
este tipo de verdad te lo digo no la
never recognized her well King I don't want to
reconocido nunca bueno Rey no te quiero
keep you any longer if you want to sleep
entretener más si te quieres dormir
Thank you very much for stopping by handsome
Muchísimas gracias por pasarte guap
Good night Yes yes we will we will
Buenas noches Sí sí ya haremos ya
do some more some other time I'm
haremos alguno más en algún otro momento
going to sleep since we
me voy a dormir ya
have something pending that by the way I
quei tenemos una pendiente que por
saw you publish on that subject that I just
cierto te vi publicar sobre el tema ese
uploaded a video that I uploaded about your
que acabo de subir vídeo que subo sobre
case uploaded yours later I'll
el caso de subido tuya el tuyo luego me
see about the Epstein case that I
lo veo sobre el caso de epstein que te
saw you publish something also on Twitter I don't
vi publicar algo también por Twitter no
piss Sia of Michael Jackson or what but but
meo Sia de Michael Jackson o qué pero
yes there is a lot of misinformation
pero si hay muchísima desinformación con
regarding that case and a lot of
respecto a ese caso y muchísima
conspiracy And the truth is that the
conspiración Y la verdad es que el caso
real case is more ago than it seems I think
real es más ago de lo que parece cre Yo
that people have taken whoever
creo que la gente ha cogido quien sea
gave them the papers because I don't
que haya sedido los papeles porque yo no
know how they can access them and they have started
sé cómo se pueden acceder y se han liado
to see maybe people who don't even
a ver a lo mejor gente incluso que no
speak the language and and they have started to see
habla el idioma y y se han liado a ver
names and they have said this one is on the
nombres y han dicho este está en la
list this other one is this other one is in
lista este otro está este otro está en
the papers of course the papers are there But
los papeles claro están los papeles Pero
because maybe a testimony comes out or they
porque a lo mejor salen un testimonio o
have asked starting  starting from the fact
han preguntado partiendo partiendo de
that there isn't even a list, I mean, it's
que ni siquiera hay una lista o sea no
not like there's a list like that.
no es que haya una lista así Simplemente
There are simply some court documents with the
hay unos documentos judiciales con las
transcripts of the Witnesses and
transcripciones de los Testigos y a
sometimes they mention someone in passing, you
veces mencionan a alguien de pasada
know, they don't even have any kind
sabes que ni siquiera tiene ningún tipo
of, for example, the Clinton thing, the
de por ejemplo lo de Clinton lo de
Clinton thing is shown in the video
Clinton lo muestra en el vídeo
literally, it's a witness who says that
literalmente es una testigo que dice que
one day Epstein told her that Clinton
un día epstein le dijo que a Clinton le
likes young girls, it's like, And what do you know, I mean, he
gustan jóvenes es como Y qué sabes o sea
could be referring to any [ __ ] That's the
podría referirse a cualquier [__] Es lo
only thing, literally, it's the only thing, it's like he
único literalmente es lo único es como
could be referring to any [ __ ], he
podría referirse a cualquier [__] cosa
could be talking about minors or
podría estar hablando tanto de menores
not, he could simply be talking about the fact
como no podría estar hablando
that he likes
simplemente que le gusta las chicas
young girls and that's it, and also that we're
jóvenes y punto y además que estamos
talking about a third-party testimony, I
hablando de un testimonio de tercera es
mean, Epstein tells this girl,
decir epstein se lo cuenta a esta chica
this girl tells it to someone at the
esta chica se lo cuenta a alguien del
trial and at the trial he transcribes it and they
juicio y en el juicio transcribe y nos
tell it to us, it's like, well, the
lo cuentan a nosotros es como en fin el
case itself is much more boring than what they
caso en sí es mucho más aburrido de lo
really intend to make it seem like, What is it,
que realmente pretenden hacer ver que
but you know, clicks and nonsense sell a lot more.
Qué es pero ya sabes venden mucho más
Yes,
los clicks y las tonterías está sí está
the subject is strong. In fact, I haven't
fuerte el tema de hecho yo llevaba sin
uploaded a video on that channel for a month and I
subir un un mes vídeo en ese canal y
think it has 100,000 views. The
creo que tiene 100000 visitas al
video will  I'll do another one so that they do
vídeo haré otro haré otro para que luego
n't tell me later that I'm leaving the channel,
no me digan que abandono el canal
handsome, a kiss, come on, let's see if
guapísimo un besito venga a ver si
we do a Stream playing at this house of yours, you
hacemos un Stream jugando a esta tu casa
have to
que me lo tienes que
tell me. Come on, nothing, what's on
decir Venga pues nada qu ha en el
live, come on, ch. Bye, ch.
directo venga ch Adiós ch
[Music]
[Música]
bye
chao